businessconsumeralliance.org 2017-06-06

# Business Consumer Alliance

#### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, fill out a form, file a complaint or respond to a complaint or post photos or other information related to a business. 

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your, name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or other pertinent information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

#### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To process transactions. In order to process a complaint, BCA may send the complaint to the BCA where the business complained about is headquartered, or refer the complaint to another appropriate government agency for handling. By completing a complaint form or sending us a request or inquiry, you are allowing us to forward your information to the appropriate business. Consumer inquiries will be forwarded to the appropriate business or agency by email, and consumers should recognize that this method of transmission may not be secure. Without submission of the requested information, BCA will not be able to process your complaint. If you post a customer review or respond to a review, we may publish that information on our website. Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  * To send periodic emails The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

#### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

#### Do we use cookies? 

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. 

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. 

#### Do we disclose any information to outside parties? 

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

#### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance 

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

#### Online Privacy Policy Only 

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

#### Terms and Conditions 

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://www.businessconsumeralliance.org/TermsOfService.aspx>. 

#### Your Consent 

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. 

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

This policy was last modified on April 15,2013 

#### Contacting Us 

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy or if you want to make changes to your personal information, you may contact us using the information below. 

Business Consumer Alliance  
P O Box 970  
Colton, California 92324  
USA  
info@businessconsumeralliance.org  
(909)825-7280
